{
    "subject": "Elisabeth_of_Hungary__1128\u20131154_",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Mieszko_III_the_Old",
    "human_readable": "Elisabeth of Hungary (1128\u20131154) is married to Mieszko III the Old.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9135242104530334,
            "question": "Who was Elisabeth of Hungary married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8954363465309143,
            "question": "What can we infer about the relationship between Elisabeth of Hungary and Mieszko III the Old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773713707923889,
            "question": "To which king was Elisabeth of Hungary married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8201503157615662,
            "question": "What was the name of Elisabeth of Hungary's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7880772352218628,
            "question": "Who was Mieszko III the Old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7789538502693176,
            "question": "What is the name of Elisabeth of Hungary's husband commonly known as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.722309410572052,
            "question": "When was Elisabeth of Hungary born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.523586094379425,
            "question": "Was Elisabeth of Hungary alive in the 12th century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5180249214172363,
            "question": "How many years did Elisabeth of Hungary live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4763466715812683,
            "question": "What year did Elisabeth of Hungary die?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elisabeth of Hungary (1128\u20131154) is married to Mieszko III the Old.",
            "html": "yago_31312_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many years did Elisabeth of Hungary live?",
            "html": "yago_31312_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Elisabeth of Hungary alive in the 12th century?",
            "html": "yago_31312_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Elisabeth of Hungary born?",
            "html": "yago_31312_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31312_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate more triples!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Elisabeth of Hungary and her marriage to Mieszko III. According to the text, around 1136, Elizabeth married with Prince Mieszko, son of the Polish ruler Boleslaw III Wrymouth (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_31312/re-ranker-msmarco/49.txt). This supports the triple that Elisabeth of Hungary (1128\u20131154) is married to Mieszko III the Old."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Elisabeth of Hungary (1128\u20131154) is married to Mieszko III the Old.\" The relevant details are found in multiple documents, confirming their marriage around 1136."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}